

CONTACT



+91-

9940766819



jumanahaseen07@gmail.c



Urapakkam, Chennai

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Vanilla JavaScript
- Figma
- Jest
- Public-Speaking
- Team-player
- Git-hub

LANGUAGES

- English
- Tamil

Jumana Haseen M

FRONT END DEVELOPER(FRESHER)

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a growing Self-taught Front end Developer with 2+ years of experience in Data Conversion, Has a Career Braek of 2 Years. Creative, sharp-minded person with leadership & coaching skills. Strong time-management skills, Great Team Player skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Conversion Chennai Steel Company Specialist
Jan 2019-July 2020

Working with clients to convert data between different formats, Effectively making data presentable and readable for client according to specifications, Translating the company's sales documents to standard format ensuring the accuracy of this process by checking for errors and correcting them.

Data Conversion Specialist HTC Global Services

May 2017-July 2017

Worked with a team of 12 members in an American Newspaper project, Converted vast amount of data in the desired format, Efficient in Meeting targets and Eased to work in a collaborative environment

EDUCATION

M.A.M College of Engineering 2012-2016

B.E Computer Science and Engineering 7.08CGPA

Seventh DAy Adventist Matriculation Higher Secondary

2011-2012 Higher Secondary School-State Board 67.5%

Private

2009-2010 Secondary School- **73.6%**

State Boardl

Projects

Coursera Projects

Project-1

Portfolio Website SELF WORK (Offsite) Sep 2022 to Sep 2022 (Full Time)

UI introduction and finished product preview. Learn how web browsing works and what HTML is. Use HTML to specify headings and paragraphs. Use HTML to specify images, small text and horizontal lines. Use HTML to add hyperlinks. Learn what CSS is and use it to control margins, background colours, text colours. Use CSS to control fonts, text alignments, hyperlink colours. Enhance your website to make it look more professional, device-friendly and ready for search engines such as Google. Upload your files to Github and make your website live to the world! Gained Knowledge of Hands on Experience in working on Cloudspace(Rhyme)

Project-link

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/CZ M77HPDHF4Q

Project-2

Design and Develop a Website using Figma and CSS SELF WORK (Offsite) Sep 2022 to Sep 2022 (Full Time)

Get familiar with the basic tools and features of Figma. Learn to design a website prototype. Learn to code your prototype into a website using HTML and CSS. Project divided into 6 tasks and working on Cloudspace is Attained

Project-link

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/3 MJ79PLCHT65

Project-3

Design and Develop a Website using Figma and CSSEdit SELF WORK (Offsite) Sep 2022 to Sep 2022 (Full Time)

Get familiar with the basic tools and features of Figma. Learn to design a website prototype. Learn to code your prototype into a website using HTML and CSS. Project divided into 6 tasks and

working on Cloudspace is Attained Build your first React WebsiteEdit SELF WORK (Offsite)

Aug 2022 to Sep 2022 (Full Time)

Understand the fundamentals of React How to build a React website Develop functional React components Develop classbased React components How to debug React websites

Project-link:

https://coursera.org/share/d16da1848b0f6947b5c01206934c6e

College-Project

Project Internship at Sanspaeril IT Services pvt.ltd for 2 months

Enterprise system has a centralized server to store and process data. The data will be stored and retrieved from database within the group of organization. In all the branch they can store and retrieve the data. Here the data will stored in the common database and the values will be retrieved using Map Reduce algorithm.

Project Based on

Java HTML CSS My-Sql Mongo-DB

Profile-links



www.linkedin.com/in/jumana -haseen-3608718b



https://www.naukri.com/mnj user/profile?id=&altresid